innovationalnewmedia.co.uk 2013-03-31

# Privacy Policy | Innovational New Media - INMedia

Innovational New Media Limited and its group of websites are committed to user’s privacy. We are registered under the Data Protection Act 1998 (number) and adhere to all rules and regulations in order to safeguard your information under these terms. If you would like to know more about the Data Protection Act please follow this link: [http://www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk](http://www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk/)

If you feel we are not abiding by our [privacy policy](http://www.innovationalnewmedia.co.uk/inmedia/privacy-policy/ "privacy policy"), or have any questions regarding the use of your data, then please email us at [data@innovationalnewmedia.co.uk](mailto:data@innovationalnewmedia.co.uk)

**Personal Information**   
Innovational New Media collects basic demographic data (Name, Region, Age, Gender, Email Address) from you as part of the registration process; we may also collect lifestyle information (including interests & purchasing habits) that are derived from your on site activity. This information is collected to help us improve the service we provide, and to help improve client relationships through targeting third party messages about products and/or services.

**Use of your Information**  
The information you provide to Innovational New Media and its group of sites maybe used by Innovational New Media to contact you with offers and information on its products and that of third parties by email, sms, and postal. We will always strive where possible, to communicate messages that are of interest to you, based on the information you provide us. This May involve the transfer of your data to other companies outside the UK and EU. By registering your information you consent to such use and transfer of data. 

If any information held on you is incorrect, or you would like to update this information; then please email us at: [data@innovationalnewmedia.co.uk](mailto:data@innovationalnewmedia.co.uk). You are within your legal right to request a copy of any data held on you by Innovational New Media, there would be a small administration charge in performing the request.

If you wish not to receive any further information from Innovational New Media or its group of websites then please send an unsubscribe request to [unsub@innovationalnewmedia.co.uk](mailto:unsub@innovationalnewmedia.co.uk). You can also unsubscribe at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of all email communications. Please allow up to 48hours for the unsubscribe process to be fully initiated.

If this business is sold or integrated with another business your details may be disclosed to our advisors and any prospective purchasers and eventually become ownership of the new company owners.

**Sponsored Surveys / Questionnaires**  
Each individual user must opt-in to the followings statement when completing their registration:

“By registering your details, you are consenting to Innovational New Media and its trading websites and its clients sending you information about products and/or services that maybe of interest to you. You also agree to the general terms and conditions and privacy policy that govern what is done with you information.”

Each questionnaire or survey is sponsored by a client, by giving a positive response to these surveys and questionnaires you are consenting to the sponsor/client sending you information about products and services. If you wish to unsubscribe to that client, you must contact them directly, or click on the unsubscribe link on all communication emails from said sponsor/client. Please note that all sponsors questionnaires and surveys are optional and a negative response can be given on all surveys and questionnaires.

**Security**  
Your Information will be stored and kept as advised by the Data Protection act. Your informational may be used as stated above, and may be passed onto any successors entitled to the business and suppliers that process the data on behalf of Innovational New Media. We endeavor to ensure the up most security on all information, however, in the case of any loss or damage experienced through the loss of data Innovational New Media cannot be accept responsibility.

We provide links to external sites, which may not be governed by this Privacy Policy. We have no control over the contents of those sites or resources, and accept no responsibility for them or for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of them. ****

**Tracking and Cookies**  
Innovational New Media and its websites may track your use of the sites through the use of cookies; this allows us to observe behavior and compile aggregate data on the website. We do this to enhance the performance and usability of the website. You can alter your personal settings on your browser to reject cookies, please be aware that this may affect certain features of the site. For further information on cookies please follow this link: [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). 

Tracking may also be used on emails sent by Innovational New Media and/or its group of websites. This maybe used to confirm the open rates and be passed onto advertisers as proof of performance.

**General**  
Under certain circumstances the force of law may require the provision of information to the legal authorities, which Innovational New Media will comply. There also may be circumstance where the release of data maybe authorized due to a complaint or misuse of website that does not comply with Innovational New Media website terms and conditions.

Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be posted on this web page. Please be aware of all the terms and conditions regarding the use of each individual website as this may effect what your information is used for. The use of Innovational New Media and its group of websites signifies that you agree to our Privacy Policy and individual site Terms and conditions.

Innovational New Media trades as the following websites: [www.dailypoll.co.uk](http://www.dailypoll.co.uk/), [www.thefridaybunk.co.uk](http://www.thefridaybunk.co.uk/), [www.facebook.apps.intilltest.com](http://www.facebook.apps.intilltest.com/), [www.lotto100.co.uk](http://www.lotto100.co.uk/)

**Useful Links**  
The Information Commissioner  
The Citizens Advice Bureau  

**Customer Service:**  
Innovational New Media  
Email: [team@innovationalnewmedia.co.uk](mailto:team@innovationalnewmedia.co.uk)  
Company Registration Number: 6560388

Privacy Policy Last Updated: 21 April 2008
